{
  "categories": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Java",
      "created-by": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "GK",
      "created-by": 2
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "question": "Who developed Java",
      "option1": "Ayush",
      "option2": "Neeraj",
      "option3": "Amir",
      "option4": "Amit"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "question": "Which of those doesn't have an index based structure?",
      "option1": "List",
      "option2": "Set",
      "option3": "Map",
      "option4": "Tree"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "question": "java.util.Collections is a:",
      "option1": "Class",
      "option2": "Object",
      "option3": "None",
      "option4": "Interface"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "question": "Methods such as reverse, shuffle are offered in:",
      "option1": "Object",
      "option2": "Set",
      "option3": "Collections",
      "option4": "Apache Common Collections"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "question": "Which of those allows duplicate elements?",
      "option1": "Set",
      "option2": "List",
      "option3": "All",
      "option4": "None"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "question": "Which allows the storage of a null key and null values?",
      "option1": "Graph",
      "option2": "Hashtable",
      "option3": "Hashmap",
      "option4": "None"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "question": "IC chips used in computers are usually made of:",
      "option1": "Lead",
      "option2": "Silicon",
      "option3": "Chrome",
      "option4": "Gold"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "question": "One kilobyte is equal to:",
      "option1": "1000 bytes",
      "option2": "100 bytes",
      "option3": "1024 bytes",
      "option4": "1023 bytes"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "question": "Which of the following is not an example of Operating System?",
      "option1": "Windows 98",
      "option2": "OS X",
      "option3": "Unix",
      "option4": "MS-Office"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "question": "Which supercomputer is developed by the Indian Scientists?",
      "option1": "Param",
      "option2": "Super 301",
      "option3": "Brahma",
      "option4": "Agni"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "question": "What kind of errors can be pointed out by the compiler?",
      "option1": "Syntax Error",
      "option2": "Semantic Error",
      "option3": "Logical Error",
      "option4": "Internal Error"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "question": "What is the control unit's function in the CPU?",
      "option1": "To transfer data to primary storage.",
      "option2": "To store program instructions.",
      "option3": "To perform logic functions.",
      "option4": "To decode program instructions."
    }
  ],
  "answers": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "questionId": "1",
      "answer": "Neeraj"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "questionId": "2",
      "answer": "Set"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "questionId": "3",
      "answer": "Class"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "questionId": "4",
      "answer": "Collections"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "questionId":"5",
      "answer": "List"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "categoryId": "1",
      "questionId": "6",
      "answer": "Hashmap"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "questionId": "7",
      "answer": "Silicon"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "questionId": "8",
      "answer": "1024 bytes"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "questionId": "9",
      "answer": "MS-Office"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "questionId": "10",
      "answer": "Param"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "questionId": "11",
      "answer": "Syntax Error"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "categoryId": "2",
      "questionId": "12",
      "answer": "To perform logic functions."
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "name": "Ayush",
      "username": "ayush@gmail.com",
      "password": "1234",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Kshitij",
      "username": "kshitij@gmail.com",
      "password": "5678",
      "id": 2
    }
  ],
  "quiz_data": [
    {
      "categoryId": "1",
      "userId": "1",
      "marks": 5,
      "totalMarks": 6,
      "dateTime": "",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "userId": "1",
      "categoryId": "1",
      "marks": "5",
      "totalMarks": "6",
      "dateTime": "13/1/2021 : 02:21:46",
      "id": 2
    }
  ],
  "admin": [
    {
      "username": "admin@1",
      "password": "admin1",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "admin@2",
      "password": "admin2",
      "id": 1
    }
  ]
}